partyearth.com 2019-08-07

# Privacy Policy | Party Earth

**Effective May 7, 2013:**

At World Travel Media LLC ("Party Earth") we feel very strongly about our customers' privacy. Any information that you give us is held with the utmost care and will not be used other than as described in this privacy policy.

Party Earth has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy on PartyEarth.com ("the Site"). The Party Earth name and reputation is built on the trust of our customers, and we hope that our commitment to online privacy will inspire the same trust in you while you are visiting PartyEarth.com.

We have adopted a set of information management guidelines that serve as the basis for our customer relationships. These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page. Please read this privacy policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use PartyEarth.com.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please e-mail us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**The Information We Collect**

We collect personal information from you on PartyEarth.com when you provide it and in some cases, from third party sources such as credit card companies in order to ensure that your credit card information is up-to-date.

**User Registration**

Registration on PartyEarth.com is strictly voluntary. To register on PartyEarth.com, you must provide your name, e-mail address, age, and geographic information. This information is required in the registration process at PartyEarth.com, but we recognize that this is your personal information and, except as we explain below, we do not distribute this information to third parties without your approval. Becoming a registered user on PartyEarth.com enables you to access Party Earth content. At any time, you may review or update the personal information we have collected from you online by logging on with your e-mail address and password and then going to your user profile.

**Email Communications**

When you sign up for a Party Earth account, we opt you in to receive emails and communications from Party Earth, its affiliates, and business partners. You can manage your email preferences and opt out of emails via your user profile or by contacting customer service at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) Note that you cannot opt out of receiving required administrative or legal notices.

**Credit Card Policy**

To simplify ordering and product fulfillment in the Party Earth Store, we request your credit card number, its expiration date and security code, and your billing and shipping address. We transmit this information safely over the Internet in encrypted form and store it on a secure server. This information is used only to bill you for and ship to you the PartyEarth.com products that you order on PartyEarth.com.

**Cookies**

PartyEarth.com employs cookies (small pieces of text stored on your computer) to recognize you and your access privileges. For example, we use cookies to allow you to log on to PartyEarth.com automatically without entering your ID and password each visit. Cookies also identify you and your preferences on our site. You may refuse to accept our cookies, but we will not be able to recognize you as a registered user, which will limit your access to the site.

**IP Addresses**

PartyEarth.com logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes.

**Third Party Advertising**

With respect to the ads appearing on PartyEarth.com, information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, is used to serve ads to you.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use your e-mail address to send you updates and newsletters periodically about new features, special offers and targeted promotional items available on PartyEarth.com. You may choose to not receive certain of these communications by so indicating in your user profile, or in response to one of our e-mails. Each communication will clearly explain how to opt out of future communications. Any demographic information that you voluntarily share with us is used to tailor PartyEarth.com to your interests. We also may share this demographic information with other companies with which we do business.

**With Whom We Share Information**

We share your personally identifiable information with intermediaries. These intermediaries use your information in connection with processing payments for online purchases and with delivery of e-mail to our registered users. We do not permit these intermediaries to use, store or retain this information for secondary purposes, unless they indicate otherwise in communications to you. From time to time we may allow some of our select partners to send you special promotional offers that we believe may be of special interest to you. You may choose not to receive these communications from our partners by so indicating in response to any of these communications, each of which will clearly explain how to opt out of future communications. You may also opt out of having your personal information shared with these third parties by sending a request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to deactivate your PartyEarth.com user account. If you do so, however, you will not be able to take advantage of many of our features, including the right to purchase items from our store; and your account may even be deactivated. We do retain the right to share and transfer all user information with a purchaser of our company or all or substantially all of our assets if that purchaser agrees to abide by the terms of this Policy.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform with the law or legal process or to protect or defend our rights or property.

**Security**

PartyEarth.com has security measures in place to help protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All information is stored in a secure operating environment. When sending sensitive information across the Internet - including purchasing information such as credit cards - we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption via Authorize.net. Internally, all customer information is protected with multiple security checks. Employee access to the system is limited to the functionality necessary for each person's job. Relevant employees are informed of our security policies and their access to applications and data on our network.

If you still do not feel comfortable about leaving your credit card information on our secured Web site, please contact our customer service department at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we'll be happy to help you with your order.

**Links**

We may provide links to third party Web sites as a service to our users. Please be aware that we cannot control and are not responsible for the information collection practices of such Web sites, which may differ from those of PartyEarth.com. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies on these Web sites before providing any information to them.

**How You Can Access or Correct Your Information**

If you are a registered PartyEarth.com user you can make changes to your personal information at any time by clicking on your user profile, or by e-mailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) At any time you can also review your personal information in your user profile.

**Questions**

Protecting your privacy is one of our highest priorities. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you may e-mail us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Consent and Opting-Out**

Upon request, PartyEarth.com will:

  1. Remove your personal and account information from our database, thereby deactivating your membership
  2. Correct personal information that you state is erroneous
  3. Permit you to "opt out" of further e-mail contact (excepting notification from PartyEarth.com of major changes to the service) while still allowing access to the site

To request a correction or cancellation, send us a message through the Contact Us form on the Site, or e-mail us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to materially change our privacy policy, we will post changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prevent that use (we will post a notification of such changes 30 days prior to their implementation). You may determine when this privacy policy was updated last by noting the "Last Updated" date directly beneath the title of this page.
